{
    "0":{"multi_choice":true,"question": "What port number is used by HTTPS?", "answer": "443", "others": ["1000", "123", "80"]},
    "1":{"multi_choice":true,"question": "What type of malware can self-replicate without user intervention?","answer": "Worm","others":["Trojan", "Virus", "None of the above"]},
    "2":{"multi_choice":true, "question": "Static variables are located in what area of memory?","answer":"Stack","others":["Heap", "Void", "Pointer"]},
    "3":{"multi_choice":true, "question": "Dynamic variables are located in what area of memory?","answer":"Heap","others":["Stack", "Void", "Pointer"]},
    "4":{"multi_choice":false, "question": "A type of malware designed to look legitimate is called a ---","answers":["Trojan", "Trojan Horse"]},
    "5":{"multi_choice":true, "question": "What x86 register points to the memory offset of the next program operation?","answer":"Instruction Pointer","others":["Base Pointer", "Stack Pointer"]},
    "6":{"multi_choice":true, "question": "What programming language is NOT considered memory safe?", "answer":"C++", "others":["Python", "Java", "Rust", "Go"]},
    "7":{"multi_choice":false, "question": "A --- is a piece of computer hardware that executes program instructions.", "answers":["CPU", "Central Processing Unit"]},
    "8":{"multi_choice":true, "question": "What type of CPU architecture does the Raspberry Pi 4's CPU use?", "answer":"ARM", "others":["X86", "AMD64", "Z80", "SPARC"]},
    "9":{"multi_choice":false, "question": "The --- is the area of a network where external-facing servers, such as Web servers are located.", "answers":["DMZ", "Demilitarized Zone"]},
    "10":{"multi_choice":true, "question": "Who is generally credited for creating the first computer worm?", "answer":"Robert Morris", "others":["Kevin Mitnick", "Kevin Poulsen", "Steve Wozniak"]},
    "11":{"multi_choice":true, "question": "An individual or group of hackers with the intent of creating social or political change are called...", "answer":"Hacktivists", "others":["Nation State Actors", "Script Kiddies", "White-hats"]},
    "12":{"multi_choice":true, "question": "Which RAID level provides both disk striping and mirroring?", "answer":"10", "others":["0", "1", "5"]},
    "13":{"multi_choice":true, "question": "Which RAID level provides ONLY disk striping?", "answer":"0", "others":["10", "1", "5"]},
    "14":{"multi_choice":true, "question": "Which RAID level provides disk striping with parity?", "answer":"5", "others":["0", "1", "10"]},
    "15":{"multi_choice":true, "question": "What port number is used by NTP?", "answer":"123", "others":["110", "25", "8080"]},
    "16":{"multi_choice":true, "question": "What port number is used by FTP for data transmission?", "answer":"20", "others":["21", "123", "443"]},
    "17":{"multi_choice":true, "question": "What port number is used by FTP for server commands?", "answer":"21", "others":["20", "123", "443"]},
    "18":{"multi_choice":true, "question": "What port number is used by DNS?", "answer":"53", "others":["80", "25", "123"]},
    "19":{"multi_choice":false, "question": "--- is the transport layer protocol that is connection oriented and provides error-checking.", "answers":["TCP", "Transmission Control Protocol"]},
    "20":{"multi_choice":false, "question": "--- is the transport layer protocol that is connectionless and does not provide error-checking.", "answers":["UDP", "User Datagram Protocol"]},
    "21":{"multi_choice":true, "question": "Many access-control list implementations come with an implicit --- at the end of the list.", "answer":"Deny Any", "others":["Allow Any", "Allow Internal", "Deny External"]},
    "22":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What is NOT an example of asymmetric key cryptography?", "answer": "AES", "others":["RSA", "PGP", "Diffie-Hellman"]},
    "23":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What is NOT an example of symmetric key cryptography?", "answer": "PGP", "others":["AES", "Blowfish", "3DES"]},
    "24":{"multi_choice": false, "question": "A(n) --- is a program vulnerability where a value is stored in a variable with less memory allocated than needed.", "answers":["Buffer Overflow", "BOF", "Overflow"]},
    "25":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "Which of these mobile operating systems are considered open-source?", "answer":"Android", "others":["iOS", "Windows"]},
    "26":{"multi_choice": false, "question": "--- is the protocol that resolves hostnames to IP addresses.", "answers":["DNS", "Domain Name System"]},
    "27":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What web attack attempts to use an end user's website authentication to execute unwanted actions upon clicking a link on a different site?", "answer":"CSRF", "others": ["Broken Authentication", "Spoofing", "Browser Hijacking"]},
    "28":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What web attack allows malicious script execution as a result of poor input sanitization?", "answer":"XSS", "others": ["CSRF", "SQL Injection", "CSS"]},
    "29":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What web attack directly causes unauthorized access to a back-end database?", "answer":"SQL Injection", "others": ["Broken Authentication", "Spoofing", "XSS"]},
    "30":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What common web issue may result in the cracking of passwords, session tokens, and more?", "answer":"Broken Authentication", "others": ["CSRF", "Spoofing", "Stale Cookies"]},
    "31":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "Hiding secret information within a form of data is called what?", "answer":"Steganography", "others": ["Cryptography", "Typography", "Calligraphy"]},
    "32":{"multi_choice": false, "question": "--- is the protocol responsible for clock synchronization on systems.", "answers":["NTP", "Network Time Protocol"]},
    "33":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What conventional username has complete administrator privileges on Unix-like operating systems?", "answer":"root", "others":["admin", "master", "key"]},
    "34":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "In a C program, the --- of a printf() call should be explicitly stated to prevent vulnerabilities.", "answer":"Format String", "others":["Endline", "Char Pointer"]},
    "35":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "As of 2020, which cloud service provider has the largest server capacity?", "answer":"Amazon Web Services", "others":["Microsoft Azure", "Google Cloud", "IBM Cloud"]},
    "36":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What word(s) describe giving a program random input data in an attempt to find a vulnerability?", "answer":"Fuzzing", "others":["Beta Testing", "Binary Searching"]},
    "37":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "A type of network device designed to control what inbound and outbound traffic is allowed is called what?", "answer":"Firewall", "others":["Switch", "Hub", "IDS"]},
    "38":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What network device forwards frames of data using source and destination MAC addresses?", "answer":"Layer 2 Switch", "others":["Firewall", "Router", "Repeater"]},
    "39":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What network device uses IP addresses to forward packets of data?", "answer":"Router", "others":["Layer 2 Switch", "Hub", "Repeater"]},
    "40":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What outdated OSI layer 2 network device generally has only one collision domain?", "answer":"Hub", "others":["Switch", "Router", "Modem"]},
    "41":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What OSI layer 2 network device generally has a collision domain for each port?", "answer":"Switch", "others":["Hub", "Router", "Modem"]},
    "42":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "A --- is a system that only monitors a single computing system for suspicious activity.", "answer":"HIDS", "others":["HIPS", "NIDS", "NIPS"]},
    "43":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "A --- is a system that only monitors a network for suspicious activity.", "answer":"NIDS", "others":["HIPS", "HIDS", "NIPS"]},
    "44":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "A --- is a system that monitors and responds to suspicious activity on a single computing system.", "answer":"HIPS", "others":["HIDS", "NIDS", "NIPS"]},
    "45":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "A --- is a system that monitors and responds to suspicious activity on a network.", "answer":"NIPS", "others":["HIPS", "NIDS", "HIDS"]},
    "46":{"multi_choice": false, "question": "What base value is hexadecimal?", "answers":["16", "sixteen"]},
    "47":{"multi_choice": false, "question":"What base value is octal?", "answers":["8", "eight"]},
    "48":{"multi_choice": false, "question": "What base value is binary?", "answers":["2", "two"]},
    "49":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What is an example of a class A private network address?", "answer":"10.128.0.0", "others":["192.168.1.1", "8.8.8.8", "172.20.0.50"]},
    "50":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What is an example of a class B private network address?", "answer":"172.20.0.50", "others":["192.168.1.1", "191.0.0.7", "10.0.0.1"]},
    "51":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What is an example of a class C private network address?", "answer":"192.168.1.1", "others":["193.168.1.1", "8.8.8.8", "172.20.0.50"]},
    "52":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What type of NAT maps multiple private IPs to one public IP and uses ports to differentiate connections?", "answer":"PAT", "others":["PNAT", "PORTNAT", "SNAT"]},
    "53":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What Linux bash command is used to list files and directories?", "answer":"ls", "others":["cat", "df", "cd"]},
    "54":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What Linux bash command is used to view what your current directory path is?", "answer":"pwd", "others":["ls", "touch", "cat"]},
    "55":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What Linux bash command is useful in viewing remaining storage space on your system?", "answer":"df", "others":["cat", "mkdir", "hdd"]},
    "56":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What Linux bash command is used to compare bytes of two files?", "answer":"cmp", "others":["diff", "cat", "ls"]},
    "57":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What Linux bash command is used to compare strings of two files line-by-line?", "answer":"diff", "others":["cmp", "ls", "cat"]},
    "58":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What Linux bash command is useful for viewing or excluding specific lines from a file?", "answer":"grep", "others":["cat", "touch", "cd"]},
    "59":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What character shortcut is useful to specify the directory path you are currently in on Linux?", "answer":". (Single Dot)", "others":["~ (Tilde)", ".. (Double Dot)", "/ (Forward Slash"]},
    "60":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What character shortcut is useful to specify the directory above your current path on Linux?", "answer":".. (Double Dot)", "others":["~ (Tilde)", ". (Single Dot)", "/ (Forward Slash)"]},
    "61":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What character shortcut is useful to specify your home directory in Linux?", "answer":"~ (Tilde)", "others":[". (Single Dot)", ".. (Double Dot)", "/ (Forward Slash)"]},
    "62":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What is the common package manager of Linux distributions such as Debian and Ubuntu?", "answer":"apt", "others":["yum", "dnf", "pacman"]},
    "63":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "Which of these languages are NOT an interpreted language?", "answer":"C", "others":["Python", "Ruby", "Javascript"]},
    "64":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "Which of these languages are NOT a compiled language?", "answer": "Perl", "others":["Rust", "C++", "Haskell"]},
    "65":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What is the name for a system that is intentionally vulnerable to distract a threat actor?", "answer": "Honeypot", "others":["Jackpot", "Rabbit Hole", "Fakesys"]},
    "66":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What system run by MITRE Corporation is a public database of vulnerabilities?", "answer":"CVE", "others":["Talos", "Zero-day", "VulnSearch"]},
    "67":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What type of phishing targets specific individuals or groups of individuals?", "answer":"Spear Phishing", "others":["Honeypotting", "Vishing", "Scan Phishing"]},
    "68":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "Phishing attacks done over the phone are sometimes referred to as what?", "answer":"Vishing", "others":["Phreaking", "VOIPing", "Spear Phishing"]},
    "69":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What packet type is the initial DHCP discover request in a DHCP transaction?", "answer": "Broadcast", "others":["Unicast", "Multicast"]},
    "70":{"multi_choice": false, "question": "What protocol does commands such as 'ping' use?", "answers":["ICMP", "Internet Control Message Protocol"]},
    "71":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "Wannacry is an example of what category of malware?", "answer": "Ransomware", "others":["Adware", "Trojan", "Spyware"]},
    "72":{"multi_choice": false, "question": "Everyday devices connected to the Internet, such as smart fridges, thermostats, and more are referred to as what three-letter acronym?", "answers":["IoT", "Internet of Things"]},
    "73":{"multi_choice": false, "question": "Spamming a network with large amounts of traffic in the attempt to degrade or disrupt service is what kind of attack?", "answers":["DoS", "DDoS", "Denial of Service", "Distributed Denial of Service"]},
    "74":{"multi_choice": false, "question": "What connects two remote private networks together over a public network to make them act like a single private network?", "answers":["VPN", "Virtual Private Network"]},
    "75":{"multi_choice": false, "question": "A --- server acts as an intermediary between a client/server connection.", "answers":["Proxy"]},
    "76":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "True or False: All VPN tunnels are encrypted.", "answer":"False", "others":["True"]},
    "77":{"multi_choice":true, "question": "True or False: It is impossible correlate traffic to a specific user when using a VPN", "answer":"False", "others":["True"]},
    "78":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "True or False: SHA-256 hashes cannot be reversed to its plaintext by cracking the algorithm itself.", "answer":"True", "others":["False"]},
    "79":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "True or False: There is no way to figure out the associated plaintext of a SHA-256 hash", "answer":"False", "others":["True"]},
    "80":{"multi_choice": false, "question": "0xD + 0x2C equals? (Answer can be expressed in hex, decimal, or octal)", "answers":["0x39", "x39", "57", "0o71", "071"]},
    "81":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "What ICMP inbound firewall configureation is most secure, while still providing a user on the network with full ping functionality?", "answer":"Allow Replies, Deny Requests", "others":["Allow Requests & Replies", "Deny Requests & Replies", "Allow Requests, Deny Replies"]},
    "82":{"multi_choice": true, "question": "Gathering intelligence using publicly available resources is referred to as what?", "answer":"OSINT", "others":["SIGINT", "OSSIM", "HUMINT"]}
}














